export default data = [
  {
      question: "Microscopes are used in medical research labs for studying bacteria or ______ that are too small to be visible to the naked eye.",
      options: ["agencies","codes","germs","indexes"],
      correct_option: "germs"
  },
  {
      question: "Lisa hopped on her bicycle and ______ as fast as she could through the dark narrow backstreets to get home after working the night shift.",
      options: ["bounced","commuted","tumbled","pedaled"],
      correct_option: "pedaled"
  },
  {
      question: "Rated as one of the top restaurants of the city, this steak house is highly ______ to visitors by the tourism bureau.",
      options: ["encountered","recommended","outnumbered","speculated"],
      correct_option: "recommended"
  },
  {
      question: "The manager ______ agreed to rent his apartment to me. Even though the agreement was not put in writing, I am sure he will keep his word.",
      options: ["barely","stably","verbally","massively"],
      correct_option: "verbally"
  },
  {
      question: "For Jerry, practicing yoga three times a week is a relaxing ______ from his tight work schedule.",
      options: ["diversion","medication","nuisance","fulfillment"],
      correct_option: "diversion"
  },
  {
      question: "Parents could be charged with neglect or abandonment if they leave their young children home alone without adult ______.",
      options: ["intuition","supervision","compassion","obligation"],
      correct_option: "supervision"
  },
  {
      question: "Walking at a ______ pace for a shorter amount of time burns more calories than walking at a slow pace for a longer period of time.",
      options: ["joyous","superb","brisk","decent"],
      correct_option: "brisk"
  },
  {
      question: "Plants and animals in some deserts must cope with a climate of ______—freezing winters and very hot summers.",
      options: ["extremes","forecasts","atmospheres","homelands"],
      correct_option: "extremes"
  },
  {
      question: "The success of J.K. Rowling is ______, with her Harry Potter series making her a multi-millionaire in just a few years.",
      options: ["eligible","marginal","confidential","legendary"],
      correct_option: "legendary"
  },
  {
      question: "The high-tech company’s ______ earnings surely made its shareholders happy since they were getting a good return on their investment.",
      options: ["robust","solitary","imperative","terminal"],
      correct_option: "robust"
  },
]